http://www.proceco.com/terms-of-use/privacy-policy

ISO 9001:2015 REGISTERED COMPANY
+ 1 800 978 6677
Customer Support
Go!
TYPHOON®-HD
TYPHOON®-PC(E)
TYPHOON®-HD
VERTICAL RECIPROCATING NOZZLE FRAME washer – (VRCP)
TURBINE ENGINE COMPONENTS
TYPHOON®-HD
TYPHOON® MB-S
TYPHOON®-PC(E)
AUTOMATED IMMERSION SYSTEMS
Automated Fluorescent Penetrant Inspection Immersion Systems - (FPI)
LOCOMOTIVE ENGINE WASHERS
LOCOMOTIVE ENGINE WASHER - (LEW)
TURBINE ENGINE COMPONENTS
Automated Fluorescent Penetrant Inspection   Immersion Systems - (FPI)
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which PROCECO Ltd. collects, uses, maintains, discloses and otherwise manages personal information of users of the www.proceco.com website ("Site") and our customers (collectively, "Users").
This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and other interactions with PROCECO Ltd.
Collection of Personal Information
We may collect personal information from Users including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form to request a quote, technical support or information, order products, or contact us about an employment opportunity or in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.
Users may be asked to provide, as appropriate, a name, company name, job title, business address, email address, telephone or fax number, and payment information.
Users may also provide us with feedback about our Site, products or services, survey responses and employment information (such as a resume, cover letter, or similar employment-related materials).
Website Information
We may collect information about Users whenever they interact with our Site.
Such information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about User's means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web Browser Cookies
Our Site may use "cookies".
A cookie is a tiny element of data that our Site sends to a User's browser, which may then be stored on a User's hard drive.
We use cookies to enhance the User experience and gather and analyze information about our Site.
Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent.
If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How We Use Personal Information
PROCECO Ltd. collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To fulfill requests for our products and services
We may use a User's name and contact information to process requests for certain services, such as to download a brochure or to request a service call or technical support. We may also use a User's contact and payment information to process product orders and ensure proper delivery. We may also use this information to improve our product and service offerings.
To improve our Site
We continually strive to improve our Site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from Users.
In addition, we use information, such as browser name, type of computer and other technical information listed above to help us understand our Site activity, and to monitor and improve the Site.
To improve customer service
We use a User's name and contact information to help us to more effectively respond to
requests for a quote or information, sales or support needs.
To process job applications
We may advertise employment opportunities on the Site. We may use a User's employment information for the purposes of processing and responding to a User's application for current and future career opportunities.
To send periodic e-mails
If a User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails occasionally that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future e-mails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How We Protect Your Information
We have adopted reasonable technical, physical and administrative measures designed to protect against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of personal information.
Disclosure & Sharing of Personal Information
We do not sell, trade, rent or otherwise transfer User's personal information without consent, except as required or permitted by law or as set out herein.
We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal information regarding visitors and Users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Service Providers
We may transfer (or otherwise make available) personal information to our affiliates or other third parties who provide services on our behalf such as to host our website, to send emails on our behalf or conduct customer research.
Sale of Business
We may transfer any information we have as an asset in connection with a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of PROCECO Ltd. or as part of a corporate reorganization or stock sale or other change in corporate control.
Legal
PROCECO Ltd. and our Canadian and US affiliates and service providers may provide personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or as otherwise required by applicable Canadian or other law.
We may also disclose personal information where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, or as otherwise permitted by law.
Third Party Websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties.
Except as provided herein, we do not provide personal information to these sites without consent.
We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible or liable for the way in which the organizations that operate such sites collect, use or disclose, secure or otherwise treat personal information. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing.
These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies.
Browsing and interaction on any other site, including sites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that site's own terms and policies.
Access to Personal Information
Users have a right to access, update and correct inaccuracies in their personal information in our custody or control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law.
To do so, Users may contact us at the information set out below.
We may request certain personal information for the purposes of verifying the identity of the User seeking access, updates or corrections to their records.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
PROCECO Ltd. has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time.
When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page.
We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.
You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site.
Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at:
1 514 254 8494
Email Us
Attention: Marketing Manager
This document was last updated on April 3, 2012.
7300, Tellier
Montréal, QC, Canada
H1N 3T7
1 800 978 6677 (Toll Free)
1 514 254 8494 (Intl.)
Email
Sign up for our newsletter
Keep up-to-date on the latest PROCECO cleaning solutions.
